https://www.shortwire.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomePrivacy PolicyLast updated: March 5, 2019ShortWire (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the ShortWire website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.shortwire.comInformation Collection And UseWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:Email addressLog DataWe collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.Compliance With LawsWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Popular Articles
1
4 Mar 2019
Understanding Various Types of Income Taxes
2
30 Jan 2019
The Benefits of Solar Energy
3
16 Jan 2019
Silver Could Be the New Gold
4
21 Dec 2018
Broaden Your Investments by Buying Gold and Silver Coins
5
18 Dec 2018
Expand Your Portfolio Buying Gold and Silver TagsBuying Rare Coins Finance Wiki Gold Gold Investment Gold Value Income Taxation Industrial Metals Inflation Hedge Investing In Precious Metals Investment Investment Opportunity Investment Portfolio Investment Strategy Investor View Journal Long Term Investment Markets Online Banking Palladium Personal Finance Platinum Platinum Metal Investing Portfolio Precious Metal Coins Precious Metals Precious Metals Demands Precious Metals Etf Precious Metals Investing Precious Metals Investment Precious Metals Market Precious Metals Outlook Precious Metals Value Rare Coin Market Rare Coins Rare Coins Investing Rare Coins Investment Rare Gold Coins Silver Silver Bullion Silver Investment Silver Metal Investing Solar Energy Solar Panels Solar Power TaxationRecommended Articles When it comes time for you to dip your toes in the water by investing in the precious metals market, some may find the task daunting. In reality, it can be a fun, profitable, and education venture for all ages. The first thing to decide is which precious metal toContinue Reading
Investing
Adding Rare Gold Coins To Your Investment Portfolio
Investing
The Value of Investing In Palladium
Investing
Prudent Rare Coin Investing
Understanding Various Types of Income Taxes
The Benefits of Solar Energy
Simple Tips for Younger Generation In Personal Financial Plan
Investing In Gold and Silver Coins
